Finding Aid for the Ana Bégué de Packman papers, 1870-1960 LSC.1491
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Miscellaneous, ca. 1850-1976; 3 boxes (1.5 linear ft.)
  - Westwood Bicentennial project, 1935, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, notes, exhibit copy and ephemera relating to a project on the history of Westwood. Includes biographical information about Packman, including a family tree in ink; and a 1935 transcription of the last will and testiment of Don Jose Maximo Alaniz.
  - Westwood Village--Sepulveda Highway fiesta, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Newspapers include mention of the opening of Sepulveda Boulevard from West Los Angeles to the San Fernando Valley. One issue of the Harbor District News, featuring a cover image of Dr. Ernest Carroll Moore.